SPEAKER_00: It's called the Fisherman and the Board. An American businessman can vacation
SPEAKER_00: to a small town in the ribs of Mexico, following the advice of his family doctor. Like
SPEAKER_00: could not sleep after a year's vacation to the first base tomorrow, it was a step
SPEAKER_00: to the dock to take a bath. A small cow with a single fisherman just applied.
SPEAKER_00: Inside were several additional yellowfin of such size. The American
SPEAKER_00: requested the Mexican for the quality of its fish.
SPEAKER_01: How long does it take to get it? -he asked.
SPEAKER_01: -Just a little while," answered the Mexican.
SPEAKER_00: Why doesn't he stay longer and fish more if I'm watching him?
SPEAKER_00: I have more than your people to support my family and give some to my friends," said the Mexican.
SPEAKER_00: many times you have been exposed to a festa, but... what do you do the rest of the time?
SPEAKER_00: Well, the Mexican looked at him and smiled. He lifted my afternoon, he fished a little with my children,
SPEAKER_01: Well, the Mexican looked at him and smiled. He lifted my afternoon, he fished a little with my children,
SPEAKER_01: I had my wife Julia for breakfast and then went to town for an all-night walk.
SPEAKER_01: Lo delero came and played guitar with my friends.
SPEAKER_01: I have a full and busy life.
SPEAKER_00: The American laughed and laughed loudly.
SPEAKER_00: -Sir, I'm a Harvard Business Administration major and I can help.
SPEAKER_01: -Sir, I'm a Harvard Business Administration major and I can help.
SPEAKER_01: -A lot of text, Mr. is very important.
SPEAKER_01: -But then what a gentleman.
SPEAKER_01: The American laughed and said, that's the best thing, he would sell his act.
SPEAKER_01: But see, I sold it.
SPEAKER_00: But see, I sold it.
SPEAKER_00: Eventually he had a fleet of fishing boats and then a middleman would come along,
SPEAKER_00: I would come an intercom with subidó and open my own in the binding machine.
SPEAKER_01: I would come an intercom with subidó and open my own in the binding machine.
SPEAKER_01: And then he said, so what?
SPEAKER_01: And then what?
SPEAKER_00: Well then, that's the best thing, I would come to my hostor and earn millions.
SPEAKER_00: Millions.
SPEAKER_00: And then what?
SPEAKER_00: Well, I would retire and move to this little fishing boat and get in late.
SPEAKER_01: Well, I would retire and move to this little fishing boat and get in late.
SPEAKER_01: I played a little with my kids, took a nap and then would go into town all night.
SPEAKER_01: to see well and play the guitar.
SPEAKER_00: to see well and play the guitar.
SPEAKER_00: -Lord, look, our wealth is here, it's there in the sun, in the sea, in the stars.
SPEAKER_01: -Lord, look, our wealth is here, it's there in the sun, in the sea, in the stars.
SPEAKER_01: at night, in the seagulls, and be with friends and quiet.
SPEAKER_00: No more of which where I started to take part in it.
SPEAKER_00: In the executive I look at him, silently, he sighed, smiled and said goodbye to my house.